Register of the June R. Genis papers
Hoover Institution Archives
June R. Genis papers
1978-1993
93052
Hoover Institution Archives
16 manuscript boxes (6.4 linear feet)
Correspondence, press releases, notes, election campaign literature, serial issues, clippings, sound and video recordings, photographs, and memorabilia relating to libertarianism in the United States and to Libertarian electoral campaigns for Congress in California.
Genis, June R., 1947-
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1993.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
American libertarian activist; Libertarian Party candidate in California for United States House of Representatives, 1988 and 1990, and United States Senate, 1992.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, press releases, notes, election campaign literature, serial issues, clippings, sound and video recordings, photographs, and memorabilia relating to libertarianism in the United States and to Libertarian electoral campaigns for Congress in California.
Libertarianism--United States.; Libertarian Party.; California--Politics and government--1951-; Free enterprise.
- Correspondence, 1988-1993
  - Letters, 1988-1992
    - Account for Better Citizenship, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 1)
    - Alzheimer's Association, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 2)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - American Citizens in Action, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 4)
    - American Life League, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 5)
    - Americans Against Prohibition, undated (Box-folder 1: 6)
    - America's Coalition for Transit NOW, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 7)
    - APB/KACE FM, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - Aragon High School, 1989 (Box-folder 1: 9)
    - Arco, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 10)
    - AT&T, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Azevedo, Paul, 1988 (Box-folder 1: 12)
    - Baase, Sara, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 13)
    - Babcock Vineyards, undated (Box-folder 1: 14)
    - Banquet, Mary, 1989 (Box-folder 1: 15)
    - Barnwell, Eileen, 1989 (Box-folder 1: 16)
    - Battemiller, Maria, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 17)
    - Bay Area Career Women, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 18)
    - Beach, George, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 19)
    - Bellamy, Lee, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 20)
    - Bethlehem Central High School, undated (Box-folder 1: 21)
    - Black Political Council, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 22)
    - Boddie, Richard, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 23)
    - Boxer, Barbara, undated (Box-folder 1: 24)
    - Cablevision Industries, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 25)
    - California Association of Marriage and Family Therapists, undated (Box-folder 1: 26)
    - California Abortion Rights Action League PAC, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 27)
    - California Democratic Party, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 28)
    - California Pro-Life Council, Inc., 1990 (Box-folder 1: 29)
    - California Public Safety League, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 30)
    - California Retired Teachers' Association, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 31)
    - Camarillo Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 32)
    - Campaign '90 Memo, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 33)
    - Carbon, Rich, 1989 (Box-folder 1: 34)
    - Carlsbad Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 35)
    - The Catholic Health Association of the United States, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 36)
    - Celebrity and Consumer Coalition for Health Freedom, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 37)
    - Center for National Independence in Politics, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 38)
    - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 39)
    - City of Menlo Park, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 40)
    - City of Pacifica, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 41)
    - City of San Jose, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 42)
    - Cohn, Armand, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 43)
    - College of the Sequoias, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 44)
    - Colby Poster Printing Co., undated (Box-folder 1: 45)
    - Common Agenda to Rebuild America, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 46)
    - Common Cause, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 47)
    - Common Sense, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 48)
    - Congressional Quarterly, Inc., 1992 (Box-folder 1: 49)
    - The Conservative Caucus, undated (Box-folder 1: 50)
    - Corlett, Michael, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 51)
    - Cornett, Dena, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 52)
    - Coronado Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 53)
    - Cromwell, Richard, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 54)
    - Cummins, Jenny, undated (Box-folder 1: 55)
    - Cusack, Lisa, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 56)
    - Daly, Dan, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1: 57)
    - Daniels-Meade, Caren, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 1: 58)
    - Deardorff, Dirk, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 59)
    - Del Norte County Community Candidate Fair, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 60)
    - Department of Health Services, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 61)
    - Dillon, Kenn, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 62)
    - Diocese of San Diego, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 63)
    - Diversified Mailing, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 64)
    - Dixon, Julian, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 65)
    - Downtown San Diego Association, 1988 (Box-folder 1: 66)
    - Educators' Committee to Re-elect Assemblyman Bill Duplissen, undated (Box-folder 1: 67)
    - Empire Broadcasting Corporation, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 68)
    - English Language Political Action Committee, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 69)
    - Erikson, Geoffrey, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 70)
    - Ernsberger, Don, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 71)
    - Fair Trade Campaign, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 72)
    - Federal Election Commission, undated (Box-folder 1: 73)
    - Federal Voting Assistance Program, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 74)
    - Foster City Chamber of Commerce, 1988 (Box-folder 1: 75)
    - Fowler, Miles, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 76)
    - Freedom, John, undated (Box-folder 1: 77)
    - Freedom of Speech, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 78)
    - Friedl, Stephen, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 79)
    - Ganino, Frank, 1989 (Box-folder 1: 80)
    - Greater Frazier Park Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 2)
    - Griffin, Barbara, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 3)
    - Hansson, Frederick, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 4)
    - Harry Singer Foundation, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 5)
    - Hartnett, James, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 6)
    - Heiser, Fred, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 7)
    - Herschensohn, Bruce, undated (Box-folder 2: 8)
    - Hunger and Homeless Action Coalition of San Mateo County, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 9)
    - Hughes, Shirley, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 10)
    - Involved!, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 11)
    - Inyokern Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 12)
    - JVM Campaign Services, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 13)
    - Kaye, Kourtney, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 14)
    - KBNN, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 15)
    - Keller, Pat, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 16)
    - KGO Radio, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 17)
    - Kopp, Quentin, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 18)
    - KQED, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 19)
    - KSRO, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 20)
    - Kumetat, Harriett, 1989 (Box-folder 2: 21)
    - KUSP, 1989 (Box-folder 2: 22)
    - Lancaster, S. E., undated (Box-folder 2: 23)
    - League of Women Voters, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 2: 24)
    - Left Coast California, undated (Box-folder 2: 25)
    - Lemoore District Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 26)
    - Lepore, Art, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 27)
    - Life and Times, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 28)
    - The Lighthouse, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 29)
    - Ling Leung, Yin, 1989 (Box-folder 2: 30)
    - Lite FM, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 31)
    - Long and Associates, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 32)
    - Los Angeles Daily News, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 33)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 34)
    - Lund, Eric, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 35)
    - Luth Research, Inc., 1992 (Box-folder 2: 36)
    - Macintosh, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 37)
    - Madera County Council, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 38)
    - Magoffin, Joe, undated (Box-folder 2: 39)
    - Marcoux, Craig, undated (Box-folder 2: 40)
    - Martin Outdoor Advertising, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 41)
    - Mexican American Political Association, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 42)
    - Meyers, Elizabeth, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 43)
    - Moorpark College, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 44)
    - Mornings on Two, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 45)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 46)
    - National Organization for Women PAC, undated (Box-folder 2: 47)
    - National Public Radio, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 48)
    - National Rifle Association, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 49)
    - National Taxpayer's Union, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 50)
    - Oakland Tribune, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 51)
    - Ogawa, Andrew, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 52)
    - Oliver, Ronald, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 53)
    - Ontario Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 54)
    - Operation Clean Congress, undated (Box-folder 2: 55)
    - Orange County Bar Association, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 56)
    - Orange County Register, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 57)
    - Organization of Chinese Americans, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 58)
    - Ormond, Lisa, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 59)
    - Pacific Bell, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 60)
    - Palomar College, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 61)
    - Palomar Community Newspapers, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 62)
    - Pauler, Steve, undated (Box-folder 2: 63)
    - Peat, Donald, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 64)
    - Peninsula Celebration Association, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 65)
    - Peninsula Times Tribune, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 66)
    - People for Reason in Science and Medicine, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 67)
    - Pico, Gerald, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 68)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 69)
    - Political Action Committee Towards Motorcycle Awareness Now, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 70)
    - Pratt, Larry, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 71)
    - Pro-Family Caucus, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 72)
    - Pro-Family Unity, undated (Box-folder 2: 73)
    - Putnam, Mark, undated (Box-folder 2: 74)
    - Rainbow Lobby, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 75)
    - Ray Hoffman Properties, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 76)
    - Registrar of Voters, Riverside, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 77)
    - Reporter, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 78)
    - Republicans for Choice, undated (Box-folder 2: 79)
    - Rios, Vincent, 1989 (Box-folder 2: 80)
    - Robbins, Michael, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 81)
    - Rosie, Rodger, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 82)
    - Salinas Steinbeck Rotary Club, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 83)
    - Samuel Adams Society, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 84)
    - San Diego Arts and Cultural Coalition, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 85)
    - San Fernando Valley Business and Professional Association, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 86)
    - San Francisco Chronicle, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 87)
    - San Francisco Examiner, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 88)
    - San Diego Downtown Association, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 1)
    - San Jose Mercury News, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 2)
    - San Mateo Times, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - Sanchez, Frank, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 4)
    - Santa Clara Voters for Choice, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 5)
    - The Santa Cruz News, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 6)
    - Santa Rosa Sun, undated (Box-folder 3: 7)
    - Sapowsky-Smith, Lisa, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 8)
    - School Resource and Career Guidance Program, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 3: 9)
    - Sierra Foothills Business and Professional Women's Network, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 10)
    - Silberg, Jay, undated (Box-folder 3: 11)
    - Silver, Richard, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 12)
    - Silver Valley Sentinel, undated (Box-folder 3: 13)
    - Slocum, Warren, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 3: 14)
    - The Sonoma, undated (Box-folder 3: 15)
    - South Bay Greens, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 16)
    - South Bay Lesbian and Gay Community Organization, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 17)
    - Souza, Geo, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 18)
    - Sovereignty, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 19)
    - Spencer, John, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 20)
    - Star Free Press, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 21)
    - State Farm, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 22)
    - Steckman, Kathy, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 23)
    - Steele, Bob, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 24)
    - Sunline Transit, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 25)
    - Sunny 102 Country FM, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 26)
    - Swanson, Jack, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 27)
    - Synergestic Mailing Services, undated (Box-folder 3: 28)
    - Thompson, Dennis, undated (Box-folder 3: 29)
    - Thornton, Edwin, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 30)
    - The Times, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 3: 31)
    - TravelPhone, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 32)
    - Trias, G. R., 1988 (Box-folder 3: 33)
    - Tryon, Tom, undated (Box-folder 3: 34)
    - Tuolomne, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 35)
    - Unitarian Universalist Church, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 36)
    - United Nations Association of United States of America, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 37)
    - United States Term Limits, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 38)
    - United Way of Orange County, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 39)
    - United We Stand America, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 40)
    - University of California at Berkeley, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 41)
    - University of California Students' Association, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 42)
    - Valley Press, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 43)
    - Ventura County Coalition for Political Representation, undated (Box-folder 3: 44)
    - Video Program Network, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 45)
    - Voter Information Clearing House, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 46)
    - Voter Participation Committee, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 47)
    - Warnick, Robert, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 48)
    - Warren, Jim, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 49)
    - WasteWatchers, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 50)
    - Weber, John, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 51)
    - Willow Glen Neighborhood Association, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 52)
    - Women's Organization Coalition, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 53)
    - Wunsch, Katherine, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 54)
    - Zschau, Ed, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 55)
    - 1990-1992 (Box-folder 2: 1)
      Scope and Contents note
      Contains letters that either do not have a recipient or sender's name, or the name is illegible.
  - Emails, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 3: 56-57)
  - Faxes, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 3: 58, 4: 1)
- Campaign File, 1978-1993
  - Agendas, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Certificates, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - Forms, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 4: 4-5)
  - Government correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Government documents, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 4: 7, 5: 1)
  - Invitations, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Libertarian Party, 1978-1990 (Box-folder 5: 3)
    Contains leaflets, pamphlets, and miscellaneous campaign materials relating to the general platform of the Libertarian Party.
  - Manuals, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 5: 4-5)
  - Petitions, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Sample ballots, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 5: 7, 6: 1)
  - Statements, June Genis, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Statements, other candidates, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Surveys, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Miscellany, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 5)
    Contains writings, notes, and leaflets relating to June R. Genis's 1992 Congressional campaign.
- Printed Matter, 1980-1993
  - Advertisements, 1992 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Clippings, 1988-1992
    - 1988 (Box-folder 7: 2)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 7: 3-4)
    - 1990 (Box-folder 7: 5)
    - 1991 (Box-folder 7: 6)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 7: 7-8, 8: 1)
    - Undated (Box-folder 8: 2)
  - Contact lists, 1992 (Box-folder 8: 3)
  - Essays, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 4)
  - Financial documents, 1992 (Box-folder 8: 5-6)
  - Letterhead, undated (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Maps, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 2)
  - Notes, undated (Box-folder 9: 3-7)
  - Pamphlets, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 9: 8-10, 10: 1-2)
  - Press releases, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - Serial issues, 1988-1993
    - @eff.org, 1992 (Box-folder 10: 4)
    - APC News, 1992 (Box-folder 10: 5)
    - Ballot Access News, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 10: 6)
    - Bay Area Firearm News, 1989 (Box-folder 10: 7)
    - California Libertarian News, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 10: 8)
    - California NORML Reports, 1992 (Box-folder 10: 9)
    - California PRA Reform Coalition Newsletter, 1992 (Box-folder 10: 10)
    - California Republic, 1991-1992
      - 1991 (Box-folder 11: 1)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 11: 2-4)
    - Carmel's Own Freedom of Speech, 1992 (Box-folder 11: 5)
    - The Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 11: 6)
    - Computers and Society, 1991 (Box-folder 11: 7)
    - Election Extra, 1992 (Box-folder 11: 8)
    - The FIJA Activist, 1989 (Box-folder 11: 9)
    - Focus, 1988 (Box-folder 11: 10)
    - Freedom Network News, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 11: 11)
    - Fully Informed Jury Amendment, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 12: 1)
    - Golden Gate Libertarian, 1993 (Box-folder 12: 2)
    - Government Waste Watch, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 12: 3)
    - The Gun Owner, 1991 (Box-folder 12: 4)
    - Imprimis, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12: 5)
    - Independent Life, undated (Box-folder 12: 6)
    - ISIL World Bulletin, 1992 (Box-folder 12: 7)
    - KUSP 88.9 FM Review, 1992 (Box-folder 12: 8)
    - Laissez Faire Books, 1992 (Box-folder 12: 9)
    - The Liberator, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 12: 10)
    - Libertarian Bulletin Board, 1993 (Box-folder 12: 11)
    - Libertarian Lifeline, 1993 (Box-folder 12: 12)
    - Libertarian Party News, 1989-1993
      - 1989-1990 (Box-folder 12: 13)
      - 1991 (Box-folder 12: 14)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 12: 15)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 13: 1)
    - The Libertarian Volunteer, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 2)
    - Liberty Bell, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 3)
    - Liberty Today, 1989 (Box-folder 13: 4)
    - Mutual Fund Forecaster, 1992 (Box-folder 13: 5)
    - Nature Conservancy of California Newsletter, 1992 (Box-folder 13: 6)
    - National Women's Political Caucus Newsletter, 1992 (Box-folder 13: 7)
    - Off Mike, 1992 (Box-folder 13: 8)
    - The Peninsula Libertarian, 1990 (Box-folder 13: 9)
    - Sacramento Association of Independent Libertarians Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 13: 10)
    - San Mateo County National Women's Political Caucus Newsletter, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 11)
    - San Mateo Libertarian, 1991-1993
      - 1991 (Box-folder 13: 12)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 13: 13-14)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 14: 1)
    - Santa Clara Libertarian, 1992 (Box-folder 14: 2)
    - Scientific American, 1991 (Box-folder 14: 3)
    - Sonoma County Pachyderm Club Newsletter, undated (Box-folder 14: 4)
    - Stanford Libertarians, 1991 (Box-folder 14: 5)
    - Update, 1992 (Box-folder 14: 6)
    - Women's Political Times, 1992 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Miscellany, 1992 (Box-folder 14: 8)
    Contains leaflets, lists, shipping labels, and other printed matter.
- Audiovisual Materials, 1991-1992, undated
  - Sound recordings, 1991-1992
    Related to Genis's 1992 campaign for U.S. Senate. Titles taken from labels on recordings.
    - "Enough Is Enough," Genis for U.S. Senate, KSTN, 30 seconds, 1992; 1 sound tape reel (Box-folder 14: 9)
    - Genis for Congress, KGO radio, three 60 second spots, 7.5 IPS, 1/2 track mono, undated; 1 sound tape reel (Box-folder 14: 9)
    - June Genis, candidate for U.S. Senate - "PEOPL" with Claire Mack, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box-folder 14: 10)
    - June Genis on Hew [Hugh] Hewitt Show, KFI, Los Angeles, 1992 October 24; 1 sound cassette (Box-folder 14: 10)
    - Side A: Nancy Lord - KGO - Gene Rusko; Side B: 1) Lord cont'd, 2) Transportation, Genis, et al., KCSM, incomplete, 1991; 1 sound cassette (Box-folder 14: 10)
    - June Genis - Libertarian Party - Foothill College, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box-folder 14: 10)
    - Genis for U.S. Senate - commercials, 1) 1 min., 2) 3 mins., undated; 1 sound cassette (Box-folder 14: 11)
    - Genis - KNRY, 1992 October 28; 1 sound cassette (Box-folder 14: 11)
    - Genis campaign calls, 1992 September 15 - October 15; 2 sound cassettes (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Floppy disks, undated (Box-folder 14: 12)
    Related to Genis's 1992 campaign for U.S. Senate. Titles taken from labels on disks.
    - San Mateo Organizations, Mac Format
    - Perot Circulation, Region 26, Inyo/Mono Counties
  - Negatives, undated (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - "Why Me? A Guide for Candidates,", undated; 1 VHS videocassette (Box-folder 15: 3)
- Memorabilia and Ephemera, 1992, undated
  - Bumper stickers, 1992 (Box-folder 15: 4-5)
  - Business cards, undated (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Posters, undated (Box-folder 15: 7, 16: 1)
  - Stamps, undated (Box 16)
  - Pins, undated (Box 16)